Previously on... “Desperate Housewives”
[欲乱绝情妻]前情提要
did you leave the door open?
你没关门么？
Is that the guy who broke into your house?
就是他闯入你房子的吗
Arrests were made... yeah,that's him.
(有人终被拘捕)  对，就是他
I just want a chance to get to know you.
我不过想有个机会了解你
Well,I don't want to know you.
可我不想了解你
Fathers were confronted...
(父亲终遭对质）
who's sister mary bernard?
Mary Bernard修女是谁
You do not want to start a war with me.
跟我较量你还嫩了点儿
Boundaries were drawn...
(较量也即将开始)
mr. Williams was responsible for your husband's death.
您丈夫的死与Williams先生有关
And everyone learned that sometimes justice is served...
(而每个人都领悟到了）  (有时候恶有恶报)
we need to call an ambulance.
快叫辆救护车
Without saying a word.
(只需要你不发一言)
There were many ways to tell Bree van de kamp was a lady.
(Bree Van de Camp的贵妇风范 处处显露）
Thank you very much.
非常感谢
She was courteous to those around her,
(她待人彬彬有礼）
she moved with elegance and grace
(她举止高贵优雅）
and she was very careful to never let others know
(而且她格外注意不在人前表露心迹）
Mrs. Van de kamp,thank you for coming on such short notice.
感谢您能赶过来
So what's happened?
发生了什么事
Have you had any luck finding george?
你们找到George了么
You see,like most well-bred women...
(像大多数教养良好的女人一样)
george is dead.
George已经死了
He committed suicide last night at a hotel.
昨晚他在宾馆里自杀了
Bree had something to hide.
(Bree也有要掩藏的东西）
Oh,um...
哦...
well,um,it was very good of you to tell me in person,truly.
非常感激你们能当面通知我 真的
Actually,uh,there's more.
事实上 还有点事儿
More?
还有？
Do you recognize this?
你认得这些东西么？
Those are my panties.How did you...
这是我的...内衣
we assume mr. Williams stole them.
我们认为这是Williams先生偷的
Where did you find them?
你们在哪儿找到的
Mr. Williams had a room filled with,um...unsavory items.
Williams先生有一个房间专门存放...
It was like a shrine.
好像一个神龛一样
"Unsavory items"?Well,what does that mean?
让人不齿的物品？我不太明白
You don't want to know.
你最好还是不要明白
Just so you're aware,the "daily tribune"
您最好留心点儿 小报的那帮家伙正在挖掘这个故事
The editor's a good friend of mine.
我有个好朋友编辑 我想我可以抹掉这个报道
I'm pretty sure I can quash it,
but you might want to tell your family what's going on,
但你最好还是告诉你的家人实情
just in case.
以防万一
What is that?
那是什么
I am so sorry. You weren't supposed to see that.
真抱歉 不该让你看见这个的
Mudge,get that out of here.
Mudge 搬走！
No,wait!Is that supposed to be me?
别 等等  这个不会是我吧？
Well...
这个不会是我吧？
it's hard to say.
不太好说
I don't understand. I mean
我不明白
what would george be doing with a life-size doll?
george拿这么个真人大小的娃娃有什么用
oh,dear lord.
哦 上帝啊
- Go ahead.
- 搬走
Oh,hold it
哦 等等
What are you gonna do with that?
你们拿它干什么
Well,until we close the file on mr. Williams,
在Williams先生的案子结束前
she's considered evidence.
这是证据
We'll have to take her back to the station.
我们要把它带回警局
I am so sorry about this,Mrs. Van de kamp.
真的非常抱歉 Van de Camp太太
I know how difficult all this must be.
我知道您很难以接受
Don't you worry about me,detective Barton.
不劳烦您担心了 Barton警官
I will be just fine.
我没事的
Yes,there were many ways to tell that bree was a lady,
(是的，Bree Van de Camp 的贵妇风范处处显露)
but the surest was to watch how she maintained her dignity
(还是要看她如何在最难堪的状况下)
in even the most undignified of situations.
(如何继续保持高贵优雅的)
-------------------------- www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents --------------------------
欲乱绝情妻 第2季 第10集
Sync: YTET-Starry -==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
-=伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Desperate Housewives Season 2 Episode 10
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=- 翻译: 七宝、少数派 校对: dene
It's a story as old as time itself--
(故事依旧是那个古老的故事)
the return of the prodigal son.
(浪子回头金不换)
And no matter how many times it's repeated...
(为何故事一遍又一遍）
or how the details might vary...
(不管细节上多大相径庭)
or how the names might change...
(也不管姓名如何改变）
the story always ends the same way...
(故事总是...)
in the tender embrace of a loving father.
(在与挚爱的父亲的拥抱中结束）
Hi,dad.
嗨 爸
Susan mayer told me she gave you some money to go to Utah.
Susan Mayer说 她给了你去犹他州的钱
Yeah,I had no idea where to look for you,though,
是啊 可我不知道上哪儿去找你
and the money started to run out,
然后钱要花光了
so I thought that maybe you'd come back here.
我想说不定你回来了
You're a smart kid.
你很聪明  我能问你个问题么
Can I ask you something?
我能问你个问题么
Of course. Anything.
当然 问吧
Well,when you left town,
你离开的时候
Mrs. Tillman said that my real mother was
Tillman太太说  我的生母是犹他州的一个吸毒者
a junkie from Utah.
我的生母是犹他州的一个吸毒者
That's right.
的确如此
So...
那...
who's my dad?
我生父是谁
I don't know.
我不知道
It could have been anyone.
谁都有可能
Thanks for the faucet.
谢谢你的龙头
This leak is driving me crazy.
漏水已经要把我烦死了
Oh,it's no rush.
哦 不着急 我装好后再给我就行
Just pay me when I install it.
Hey,there!
嗨 大伙
Have you seen today's paper?
看今天的报纸了么
No,not yet.
没 还没
Ohh. There's a follow-up on that guy you caught last week.
哦 有一篇你上周抓的那个人的跟踪报道
"Police seek help in identifying mystery vagrant."
"警方寻求协助指认神秘流浪汉"
They don't know the man's name yet?
他们还不知道那人的名字么
They're not even sure that he knows how to talk.
他们甚至怀疑他根本不会讲话
Think they're going to hold him in the psych ward
估计警方把他送到精神病院看护  直到他们查出他的身份
until they figure out who he is
直到他们查出他的身份
Well,I will certainly rest easier knowing that
知道他不会在咱们这流窜
he's not roaming around our neighborhood.
我晚上睡觉就踏实多了
see you!
拜拜！
Thanks again for the faucet.
再次感谢你的龙头
Sure.
不谢
What are we gonna do about Caleb?
我们该拿Caleb怎么办
Obviously,we are going to go and get him
很显然 我们要把他弄出来
- Where are my cuffs? - Bottom drawer.
我的手铐呢  在底层抽屉
Ah.
啊
So when do I tell people you'll be back?
我该告诉别人你什么时候回来
Couple,maybe three days.
两周 或者三周吧
What the hell's this?
这是什么鬼东西
It's the ball gag.
球形嘴塞
I thought you wanted it.
不是你要的么
We do not recycle ball gags.
我们不回收用过的球形嘴塞
Take a look at the teeth marks.
看这牙印儿
it's gross.
真恶心
I'd like to think that we're better than that.
我们该用好一点儿的
Hey, Monroe?
喂 Monroe
You sure you don't want any help?
你真不用我帮忙么
The guy's dangerous.
他很危险
He's a half-wit,Jerry.
他是个弱智 Jerry
If I can handle you,
要是我能搞定你
I can handle him.
我就能搞定他
So he poisoned Rex?
这么说他毒死了Rex？
Sweet,little George Williams.
我们善良的小George Williams
Well,it turns out he wasn't so sweet after all.
看来他实际上并不怎么善良
Anyway,there's a chance that some of this may wind up in the paper,
总之 搞不好这件事会上报纸
so I wanted you to hear it from me first.
所以我想你们先从我这里听到
Bree,I'm so sorry.
bree 我和遗憾
Yeah,like you haven't been through enough.
是啊 就好像你受的苦还不够多似的
God,and he's our pharmacist.
天哪 他是我家的药剂师
It's enough to turn you holistic.
真是知人知面不知心
I know this sounds awful,
这么说听起来有点狠
but I'm kind of glad the guy's dead.
但我真高兴他死了
Oh,I hope that little creep suffered.
我希望他吃了苦头
Well,we'll never know.
我们没法知道了
That's Andrew back from camp hennessey.
Andrew从Hennessey营地回来了
I've got to go.
我得走了
Does he know yet?
他知道了么
He hasn't got a clue.
他还蒙在鼓里呢
How do you think he's gonna react?
你想他会怎么反应
All right,what the hell is going on?
行了 发生什么事儿了
I know you didn't take me out of kid jail for my health.
我想你不是为了我的健康 才把我从儿童监狱里叫回来的
I'll get back to you later.
咱们晚点儿再见
So are the police sure?
警方确定么
Yeah.
是的
They found data in George's personal computer
他们在george的电脑上查到了数据
and also records at his pharmacy that
还有他药房的纪录
pretty much proves that he was poisoning your father.
足以证明他毒害了你父亲
Did they say why he killed him?
他们说他为什么谋杀他了么
Well,the detective seems to think he was trying to
警探认为他想扫除你父亲这个障碍
get your father out of the way so...
he could marry me.
这样他就能娶我了
Honey,please use your coaster.
宝贝儿 把它放在杯垫上
That's gonna leave a ring.
会留下水印儿的
My father was murdered because of you,
我爸爸因为你被谋杀了
so as far as I'm concerned,
所以我想
you no longer get to tell me what to do.
你没资格再告诉我该干什么
Andrew,that is not fair.
Andrew 你这么说就太不公平了
You brought that psycho into our house!
是你把那个疯子带回咱家里的
You sat him down at our table.
是你请他在咱家的桌子上吃饭的
Just how fair do you expect me to be?
你还要我怎么公平
Andrew,George williams fooled a lot of people.
Andrew George Williams 蒙骗了很多人
Yeah,well,he didn't fool me.
是啊 他怎么没蒙骗我啊
Andrew,I'm not trying to minimize my part in this.
Andrew 我不是想推托我得责任
Believe me,I hate myself for what's happened.
相信我 我很后悔
Now we have something in common.
很好 现在我们有一个共同点了
Oh,by the way,
哦 对了
I'm gonna call my friend justin
我要打电话给我的朋友Justin
and have him come over and spend the night tonight.
让他过来我们家过夜
Justin? Is he a friend of yours from school or church?
Justin? 他是你学校的朋友还是教堂的？
What kind of friend is he?
什么朋友？
The real good kind.
特别好的那种
Andrew,it is inappropriate for you to have somebody over.
Andrew 这不太合适吧  你才刚回家
You just got home.
你才刚回家
Like I said,
我说了
you don't get to tell me what to do anymore.
我干什么你再也管不着了
You came.
你来了？
Did I have a choice?
我有选择么
Well,sure.
当然了
Because at the hospital,you sounded like you were
在医院的时候 你听起来似乎
into having some kind of a relationship with you.
准备要威胁我和你发展什么关系
That was just the heat of the moment,
我当时就是火大了
and once you get to know me,you'll understand that
只要你开始了解我了
I am not the kind of person who could ever,ever resort to blackmail.
你就知道我不是那种 会威胁勒索别人的人了
Well,I wish you'd made that clear in the hospital.
你要是在医院早这么说
Could have saved me a trip.
我就不用费事过来了
So are you coming in?
你要进来么
Well,I got a lunch hour to kill.
我午休时间也没什么可干的..
That was my first halloween.I was 2.
这是我第一次过万圣节 两岁时候
What do you think I am?
你猜我在扮什么
I don't know
不知道
Oh,come on,just guess.You can tell.
行了 猜猜 你能猜出来的
Uh,a homeless person?
阿...流浪妹？
No,Addison,I'm a chicken.
不是 Addison 是只鸡
See? Those are feather shanging around.
看到了么 我身上都是羽毛
Oh. I thought that was supposed to be trash.
哦 我还以为那些是垃圾呢
Uh,look,are we done here?
好了 你还有事么
You haven't even finished your coffee.
你还没喝完咖啡呢
I got to get back to work.
我该回去工作了
Oh,well,we--we haven't even finished the high school years.
哦可...我们还没说完高中时代呢
I wanted to show you this one.
我想给你看这张
This was from the father-daughter dance.
是“父女共舞"时候照得
I had to take my mother'shairstylist.
我不得不找妈妈的发型师顶替
What do you want from me,susan?
你到底想要我怎样 Susan
Well,I-I just want to share more than our D.N.A. I...
我只是想除了基因以外
I wanted to have a relationship with you.
还能和你分享一些东西
None of this means anything to you?
这些对你来说一点意义都没有么
I'll take the hobo picture.
那我就拿这样流浪汉照片好了
Actually,it was...fine.
那其实是...好吧
What's this?
这是什么
Our company insurance policy.You ever bother to read it?
我们的公司保险政策 你读过么
I'm going to say no,but don't tell.
我要说:没有 但别告诉别人
We have day care, Ed, day care.
我们有日间寄托政策 ED  日间寄托阿
Do you realize that since we fired half the staff,
你意识到自从我们开除了一半人力
you and I have barely left the building?
你和我就几乎很少出这幢楼么
My kids are forgetting who I am.
我的孩子都快忘了我是谁了
I hear you.I have 17-month-old
可不是么 我有个17个月大的孩子
who I haven't actually seen awake in weeks.
我都好几个礼拜 没在她醒的时候看过她了
See? All we need isa minimum participation
看吧？ 我们只需要 16个孩子的参与就行了
of,uh...16 kids.
My kids,your baby,
我的孩子 你的孩子
sally in accounting has three,
会计部门的Sally有三个
that new guyin human resources has two
人力资源部门的那个新来的有两个
and we hit the mother lode with the mormon receptionist.
再加上个摩门教的接待员 我们算采到母亲矿了
She just popped out number 6.There. 16.
她刚生了第六个孩子  全了 十六个
15. My wife won't do it.
十五个 我老婆不会同意的
No,I'm telling you,this day care thing is a non-starter.
没戏 我告诉你吧 日间寄托真的没戏
Fran won't even let anyone else hold the baby.
Fran甚至不让别人碰孩子一下
Well,she won't just take sometime off for a couple of hours?
她连一天休息几个小时都不肯么
Lynette,if I hadn'tcut that umbilical cord with my own two hands,
Lynette 要不是我亲手剪断了她的脐带
I swear they would still be attached.
她肯定还让它连着呢
But if you want to try...
但你要是想试试
more power to you.
随你的便
You! What the hell did you do with my husband?!
你！  你跟我老公干了什么了？！
Please restrain yourself,gabrielle.
请控制住情绪 Gabrielle
You're in a house of god.
你是在教堂
Tell me where he is!
告诉我他在哪儿
Everywhere,of course.
无处不在阿 很显然
Not god,my husband.
不是上帝 我老公
Gaby,what are you doing here?
Gaby 你在这儿干什么
I was just about to ask you the same thing.
我正要问你呢
You were supposed to meet me at the spa.
你本该在Spa等我的
I was just helping sister mary with the mailings for the fund-raiser.
我在帮Mary修女整理捐助者的信件
The church is about to senda relief team to Botswana
教堂要派一个救济小组去博茨瓦纳
to help with the drought.
帮助缓解干旱的问题
That's your excuse?
这就是你的借口？
We missed side-by-side water massages.
我们错过了一次情侣水中按摩
I had to book them weeks in advance.
我要好几个礼拜前预约呢
Okay,you missed a massage.
行了 不就是个按摩嘛
It's unfortunate,but there are people dying in Botswana.
我也不想 但博茨瓦纳的人们生命危在旦夕了
There are going to be people dying in this church
你再不把那付慈善家的丑脸撕掉
if you don't wipe that patronizing look off your face!
这个教堂就要有人危在旦夕了
What is your problem?
你干什么
Sister mary,will you excuse us,please?
Mary修女 你能离开一下么
Certainly.
当然
We are supposed to be working on our marriage,carlos,
我们本该改善我们的婚姻 Carlos
but we can't do thatas long as our lady of perpetual stick-up-her-butt
但如果那个无处不在的大屁股淑女 总让你担忧什么口渴的孤儿
has you worrying about thirsty orphans.
我们就没法改善
You're blaming sister mary for the tension in our marriage?
你把我们婚姻的问题 怪在Mary修女身上？
She wants us fighting.
她巴不得我们吵架
She wants you to get tired of me
她巴不得让你厌倦我离开我
and walk out so she can have you all to herself.
她巴不得让你厌倦我离开我  她好把你据为己有
That's crazy. She's a nun.
你真是疯了 她是个修女
She may wear a habit and the beads,
她是穿着修道服挂着念珠
but at the end of the day,
但到了晚上
she is still a woman,just like me,
她毕竟还是个女人 跟我一样
and I know what I'm capable of.
而我很清楚我能做出什么
She is a woman...
她确实是个女人
but she is nothing like you.
但她可跟你一点也不一样
Carlos,where are you going?
Carlos 你去哪儿
Carlos!
Carlos
You look tense,gabrielle.
你似乎很紧张啊 Gabrielle
Perhaps you should think about getting a massage.
或许你该考虑做个按摩
hi, Susan,it's Addison. Are you there?
嗨 Susan 是我Addison 你在么
Hi. Hi,yeah,I'm here.
嗨 嗨 是 我在
Good. You're home.
正好 你在家
Uh-huh. What's up?
嗯 怎么了
You know you were saying you wanted to be part of my life?
你不是说你想成为我生活的一部分么
Yeah.
是啊
I'm at the police station.
我在警察局
I need you to come bail me out.
我需要你保释我出去
Solicitation? You were arrested for solicitation?
嫖娼？ 你因为嫖娼被抓了？
It was entrapment.I'm the victim here.
这是陷阱 我是受害者
But you were with a prostitute.
但你跟一个妓女在一起
Apparently not.
还真不是
I asked her three times--"are you a cop?"
我问了她三次 "你是警察么?"
They got to tell you,but she didn't say "boo."
本该告诉我的， 但她没说
I thought this was America!
我还以为这里是美国呢
Addison,you just got caught paying for sex.
Addison 你嫖娼被抓了
Now is not the time to wrap yourself in the flag.
现在可不是你爱国的时候
Don't give me that look.
别这么看着我
It wasn't my fault.I'm sorry.
这不是我的错
How is trying to pick up a hooker not your fault?
抱歉 想要找妓女怎么会不是你的错
I was at the store,I was working on my computer
我在店里 正用电脑呢
and then,you know,they have these ads?
然后 你知道他们那种广告？
They pop up on the screen and they ask if you want to have a hot date.
问你要不要一次火热约会
Well,it gets a fellow worked up.
那能不诱人么
Can't you just go home and have sex with your wife like a normal person?
你就不能像别人一样 回家和你老婆做爱么
She's a 68-year-old woman.
她都60多岁了
That bell stopped ringing for me years ago.
那道门儿好几年前我就想不起来开了
Oh,my god.Stop. Right now.
哦 天哪 停 别说了
I'm gonna gopay this thing.
我去交钱
So am I off the hook now?
那我们清了吧？
What?
什么
This whole father-daughter thing,
就是这套什么父亲女儿的事儿
we're done,right?
我们完事儿了对吧
Thursday,coffee at 2.Be on time.
星期三 2点来喝咖啡 准时
Don't take this the wrong way,but are you dim?
别误会我 但你是不是瞎子
Okay,I didn't exactly love what I found out about you today,
好吧 我确实对今天认识到的你不怎么满意
but the goal was to learn,not to judge.
但目的在于认识 不在评判
I bring the coffee.
我带咖啡
That crap you made burnt a hole in my stomach.
你煮的那破玩意儿把我的胃都喝坏了
This is tunde.
这是Tunde
He lost both his parents to this drought.
他在这次旱灾中失去了双亲
In fact,water is always scarce in botswana.
事实上 博茨瓦纳一直是缺水的
The national currency is called the pula or raindrop...
他们国家的货币叫做普拉 也叫 雨点
hello, Gabrielle. What brings you here?
你好 Gabrielle 你怎么来了
I'm concerned about the drought in Kenya.
我很关注肯尼亚的旱灾
Botswana.
博茨瓦纳
Yeah,and you?
对 那你呢
Well,I'm organizing this relief trip.
我组织这次救济之行
We leave in a week.
我们一周内就出发了
Well, Bon voyage,father.
bon voyage 神父 (法语:旅途愉快）
I'm not going myself.
我不是独自前往
We had to scale back our relief efforts this year.
我们今年的救济行动不得不缩水了
We even had to cut a few of the aid workers from the trip.
我们还要减少同行的工作人员数量
Sister Mary,sister Gret awere so disappointed.
Mary和Gretawere修女非常失望
If you just want to hand some of...
如果你想要发放一些...
sister mary was going on the trip?
Mary修女本来要去的么
Well,sister mary always goes for at least a few months,
她总是至少去几个月的
but when our funding came up short,
但我们的资金不足
she graciously offered to step aside,
她很高尚的提出退出此行
said there's plenty of god's work to do here.
说在这里还有很多上帝的工作要做  谢谢 Carlos 我很感激
Thank you, Carlos. Appreciate it.
谢谢 Carlos 我很感激
I bet she did.
她可不是嘛
How much cash are you short,father?
你们缺多少钱 神父
We plan to set up a modern system of irrigation.
我们计划建立一个现代的灌溉系统
I'm sorry to interrupt,sister mary,
不好意思打扰一下 Mary修女
but I have an announcement.
但我要宣布一件事
I have just received a donation of $8,000,
我刚收到了一份8千元的捐助
which means that sister Mary and sister Greta
也就是说Mary修女和Greta修女
will be able to join our relief trip to Botswana.
可以加入我们这次的救济之行了
it just goes to show angels are everywhere.
这说明了天使无处不在
Hey. I'm here to see Lynette Scavo.
嗨 我来见 Lynette Scavo
Oh,hi. Excuse me. Hi.
哦 嗨 失陪一下 嗨
I'm lynette.You must be Fran.
我是Lynette 你一定是Fran
Hi. Ed said you needed to talk to me.
嗨 Ed说你要和我谈谈
I couldn't imagine about what.
我猜不出是关于什么
Oh,well,come on in my office.
哦 来 到我办公室说吧
You want me to put my daughter in day care?
你想让我把孩子送到日间寄托？
But I'm a stay-at-home mom.
但我是个全职妈妈啊
I'm not suggesting that you sign her up for all day.
我不是建议你让她一天都寄托在这
Maybe just a couple of hours in the afternoon.
也许就下午的几个小时
Wouldn't that be great?
那不是很棒么
Have some time to yourself, relax, unwind?
自己独享一些时间 放松 缓解一下压力
I don't need to unwind. I love taking care of little Mindy.
我没什么压力可缓解的  我喜欢照顾我的小Mindy
Oh,of course,of course,
哦 当然了 当然了
but we all have days when we're starting to lose it.
但 我们都总有一天受不了的
Wouldn't it be nice to have some place to take her
在你想要捏死她之前
before you want to strangle her?
有个地方可以寄托不是很好么
I cherish every moment I spend with her,truly.
我和她在一起的每一秒钟我都很珍惜
Really?
是么
Yeah. Look,I'm gonna level with you.
是啊 听我说  我跟你实话实说把
Parcher and Murphy can't have a day care center
Parcher&Murphy公司 不会设立寄托中心
unless we haveat least 16 kids
除非有16个以上的孩子
and without little Mindy,we only have 15.
没有Mindy 我们只够15个
Well,that's not my problem.
这就不是我的问题了
Okay. Okay. I just thought I'd give it a shot.
好吧 好吧 我就是想试试看
Well,I wish I could help you,but I can't.
我希望能帮上你 但真抱歉
Okay.
好吧
- Lynette - Yeah
Lynette 我能问你个问题么
- Can I ask you something? - Yeah
Why did you have kids if you weren't gonna raise them?
你不抚养孩子为什么还要生孩子呢
Excuse me? Well,I just don't understand who
我就是不能理解有些女人说想当母亲
say they want to be mothers,
but then hand their kids over to glorified babysitters.
却把孩子交给美其名曰得“保姆”
I work because my family needs me to.
我的家庭需要我我才工作的
Oh,dear,I've upset you, and that wasn't my intention.
哦 亲爱的 我让你不高兴了  我本意不是这样的
I bet.
当然了
Make no mistake,I'm a good mother.
别错怪我了 我是个好母亲
That's the difference between us--
这就是我们的区别
I couldn't settle for being a good mother.
做个好母亲不是我的目标
I want to be a great one.
我要做个满分母亲
Bye-bye.
再见
Oh,hi,alberta.How are you?
哦 嗨 Alberta 你好么
Were you the one that sent out those neighborhood watch pamphlets?
是不是你发放得那些小区巡逻手册的？
I was wondering if maybe you had any extra copies.
我想问问你还有没有额外的
Or I'll just borrow one from somebody else. Thanks.
或者我就管别人借一份吧 谢谢
Yep,looks like carol'spenmanship.
没错 看上去就是Carol的笔迹
This is ridiculous. What does she think,we're having an affair?
这简直太荒唐了 她难不成以为我们在搞婚外恋？
Well,she probably saw you drop me off yesterday,
也许她昨天看见你送我 就以为是了
and she assumed the worst.
Well,now you're gonna have to tell her the truth.
那么你得告诉她事情的真相
Oh,no,no,no. I'd catch holy hell.
不 不 不 我才不去惹事呢
Oh,so you want me to catch it for you?
难道要我去惹事？
I mean, you, yourselfs aid she's crazy.
你自己都说了她有点疯狂
I don't want to wake up tomorrow morning and find my tires slashed.
我可不想明天早上起来 看见我的车胎被扎破了
All right. I'll talk to her.
好吧 我和她说
Hello, Edie. Do you have something you'd like to say?
你好啊 edie 有什么要说的吗？
No. That pretty much says it all.
没有 我看那个字基本上概括我要说的了
Sister Mary,what a lovely surprise.
mary修女 原来你在啊
Well,I couldn't leave withoutsaying good-bye, Gabrielle.
我可不想不作道别就走呀 gabrielle
Oh,that's so sweet.
你人真好 我会想念你的
I'm sure not half as much as you're gonna miss your husband.
恐怕你更想念你的丈夫吧
- Huh? - Don't freak out.
别吃惊 我要去博茨瓦纳了
- I'm going to botswana. - What?!
别吃惊 我要去博茨瓦纳了  什么？！
Sister Mary needs a companion.
mary修女需要有人陪同去
What happened to sister Greta?!
greta修女怎么不去？
I was gonna go with sister Greta,but the region is so volatile,
本来是要和greta修女去的  但是那个地方比较动荡
I decided I'd feel much safer with a male companion.
有个男性伙伴陪同安全一点
Carlos,you can't do this.
carlos 你不能去, 你不能就这么去非洲
You can't just goto Africa.
Honey,I'm only gonna be gone for two months.
亲爱的 我就去两个月而已
This journey is important for me.
这次旅行对我很重要
I want to be one of god's soldiers.
我要成为上帝的战士之一
And you will be one, Carlos.
你会的 carlos
After you see the devastation over there,
到了那看到那的灾情后 你会彻底改变的
you're never the same.
You see how selfish your old life is
你会看到自己以前是多么的自私
and you just want to get rid of everything that reminds you of it.
你会摆脱那些让你想起过去日子的一切
Oh, Gosh. I should get goingand start packing.
天啊 那我得立刻开始收拾了
We leave in less than a week.
还有不到一周的时间就要出发了
I should probably send a thankyou letter to my parole officer.
我应该给我的假释官发封致谢函
He's being a real mensch about this.
这件事上他一直都很支持我
I may be a catholic,but I am so not above slapping a nun.
但我实在忍不住要抽你这修女一耳光
Go ahead.
打呀
Do it.
Just make sure you hit hard enough to leave a mark.
使点劲 留下个手掌印
Yeah. I didn't think so.
谅你也不敢打
Kiss the kids good night and I'll see themin the morning
跟孩子们说晚安 明早再见
Okay,yeah. I love you,too. Bye-bye.
我也爱你 再见
I'm sorry about the day care thing, Lynette,
日托的事我很抱歉 lynette
but Fran hardly ever lets me hold the kid.
但是fran几乎不让我抱孩子
You know,since day one,all I ever got was,
你知道嘛 自打第一天起 我能做的就是听她说
"support the head,support the head."
“托住头部 托住头部”
I think I know how to support a damn baby head.
我难道连个婴儿的头 都不知道怎么托住吗？！
Ohh,let's just--let's just do this.
哦 我们 我们还是继续工作吧
I don't want to be here all night.
我可不想一晚上都呆在这
you're Mindy's father.
可你是mindy的父亲啊
You have a right to spend time with her.
你也有权利和她在一起
I know,but what can I do?
我知道 可我又能如何呢？
You could stand up to Fran.
你应该直面fran
If you don't,you'll just become more resentful,
你要不这样 你就会越来越充满怨恨
she'll get nuttier.
而fran也会越来越得寸进尺
And without a father figure,
而且孩子成长中没有父亲陪伴
poor mindy will grow up to be a stripper.
可怜的mindy长大后 很可能成为一个脱衣舞女
A stripper?
跳脱衣舞？
There's science to back that up.
这可是科学研究证明的
You know what?
好吧
You go ahead and push the button on this day care thing, Lynette,
你继续张罗日托的事 lynette
and count Mindy in.
把mindy也算上
Yeah,I'll handle Fran.
我来对付fran
You're doing the right thing, Ed,
为了小mindy 你算是做了件好事
dude,what if your mom walks in?
要是你老妈突然进来怎么办？
She won't.
她不会的
You don't know that.
这可说不准
Just wait till everybody's asleep.
还是等他们都睡着了吧
Seriously.
说真的
I'll make it worth your while.
我不会让你白等的
You better.
那最好了
I wish she would walk in on us,
我倒希望她能突然进来
just to see the expression on her face.
到时候看她什么表情
God,I hate her so much.
我恨死她了
Still, though,she's your mother.
不过她怎么说也是你老妈呀
Don't you sort of have to love her?
儿子不是应该爱老妈嘛？
Last year,when she found out that I like guys,
去年 她知道我喜欢男的 惊恐的要命
she freaked out.
She said that if I didn't change, I'd be going straight to hell,
她说我要是不悔改 我就要下地狱
so since I knew that I couldn't change,
既然我没法改 我就想
one day,my own mother was gonna stop loving me,
既然我妈不爱我了
so I decided to stop loving her first.
我也没必要爱她了
That way,it wouldn't hurt so bad.
这样的话 大家心里也就平衡了
She didn't know what she was saying.
她说那话也许不是当真的
Yes,she did,
不 就是当真的
so now she's gotto be punished.
她要为此受到惩罚
How are you gonna punish her?
那你怎么罚她？
One day,she'll slip up,
她终有一天会疏忽
and I'll have something against her
到时候我就有她的把柄抓在手中
and when that happens,
只要有了这个
I'm gonna take her down so hard,she'll never get back up.
我就可以一下子击倒她 让她永世不得翻身
It may take you a while to get something on her.
要想抓她把柄可不容易啊
That's Okay.
没关系
I don't mind waiting for the things that I want.
等待自己期待的东西 我有耐心
Lynette,hey,hey.Look who's here.
Lynette 嘿嘿 看看谁来了
You know,the day care room won't be ready until next week at the earliest.
可日托用的房间最早 也得下周才能准备好呀
If I had waited,I might have lost my nerve.
我要是再等下去 就快疯了
I had a window.
我逮着了一个机会
Fran was in the shower,so I just grabbed the baby and ran.
Fran在洗澡  所以我就趁机把孩子带出来
You took the baby without telling Fran?
你没告诉fran就把孩子带出来了？
I refuse to be bullied by that woman. You were right.
我可不想被那个女人欺压  你说的没错,Mindy是我的女儿
Mindy is my daughter,I wanted to spend time with her.
你说的没错,Mindy是我的女儿  我想和她处处 我有这个权利
I have that right.
我想和她处处 我有这个权利
Um,Ed,the lobby just called and your wife's on her way up
呃 Ed 楼下大厅打电话说 你妻子正要上来
and she seems pretty angry.
怒气冲冲的样子
Oh,man.
哦 天啊
- Here. Hold mindy. - Oh.
你抱好Mindy
Let me handle this.
我来处理
Oh,I was planning to.
哦 我自己本来想去处理呢
I thought Mindy had been kidnapped!
我还以为Mindy被绑架了！
I left a sticky note.
我留言说了
I wasn't looking fora sticky note,ed!
我不是在找什么留言条 Ed！
I was looking for my missing child!
我在找我失踪的孩子！
She's my child,too,and she's staying here,
她也是我孩子呀 她就待在这了
just a few hours a day.
几个小时而已
- You,give her to me.
- 你 把孩子给我
No,I made a decision.
不行 我决定了
Yeah? Okay,watch me make a decision.
是嘛 我给做了个决定
I'm done with this marriage.
这日子没法过了
I'm taking my baby and I'm getting on a plane to pittsburgh.
我要带走孩子 坐飞机去匹兹堡
- You wouldn't dare! - You think you miss mindy now,
你不是很想Mindy嘛
wait till we're livingwith my mother!
我们去我妈家住后 还看你想不想！
- I'll fight you on this. - Yeah? Try...
我会和你争的
as Lynette saw her dreams of day care about to board a plane to pittsburgh,
眼看着日托之梦要随之破灭
- You're crazy,you know that?!
- 你疯了
Yeah! I'm crazy to think...
是嘛 我就是疯狂到...
she decided this flight would have to be grounded.
lynette不得不想个办法 让飞机去不成匹兹堡
You don't scare me.
你吓不住我的
Oh. Oh!
What the hell is she doing?!
她在干吗？！
Open up! Give me my baby!
把门打开 还我孩子！
- Good thinking,lynette!
- 你真有法子 Lynette！
I am not on your side,ed
我可不是支持你 Ed
- You're not?
- 不是?
No,I am on mindy's side.
不是 我是为Mindy着想
She is the one caught in the middle,
她现在处境两难
and I'm not letting you two have her until you calm down.
除非你冷静下来 否则我不会交出孩子来的
I want my damn child.
你乖乖的把孩子给我！
Lynette,I have tom on line two.
Lynette Tom在2线找你
Pat, can you see here I'm holding a baby hostage?!
Pat 没看见我这正忙着呢嘛
I will call back!
我会打过去的
All right,that's it.
好吧 既然这样 我只好报警了
- I'm calling the police. - Oh,for god's sakes!
好吧 既然这样 我只好报警了  算了吧 lynette又不会伤着我们孩子
Lynette'snot going to hurt the baby!
算了吧 lynette又不会伤着我们孩子
No,and you're gonna get herback a whole lot faster
当然不会 如果你仔细听我说 我会把孩子还给你的
if you will just listen to me,okay?
Listen,and you?All right,good.
还有你也听着 好的
So first of all, Ed,stealing the baby was really stupid.
首先, 偷带孩子出来是不对的
- Thank you.
- 谢谢
You're welcome.
不客气
You need to find a better way to communicate with your wife.
你应该找个更好的方式跟你妻子交流
And, Fran,I know what the pressure of trying to be
fran 我知道你一直想做一个 完美超级母亲 压力一定很大
a super parent does to your head.
You can take a break and be a great mom.
你可以休息一下照样做一个好母亲
Doesn't this little sweetheart deserve a well-rested mommy?
难道这个可爱的小家伙就不应该 有一个休息得当的母亲吗？
Well,I guess the pressure does get to me a little.
说的也是 压力的确很大
And it's Okay to admit that.
你能承认真好
This is communication. This is good.
这才叫交流嘛 很好
Why don't you guys go down to the lobby,
你们不如去楼下大厅边喝咖啡边聊吧
talk it out over some coffee?
Uh,what about Mindy?
Mindy怎么办？
We've got day care!
我们有日托呀！
We've got day care
I called earlier from the spiritual outreach program?
你好 我之前打过你们电话 我是“心灵辅导”项目的
Hi. Piano player,right?
你好 钢琴家 是吧
This is so generous of you.
你真好
There it is.
他就在那 不是什么大型演奏会
It's not exactly a concert grand.
I should warn you,
不过我得事先说明下
on the whole,our patients are generally unresponsive,
我们的病人一般来说反应迟钝
so I hope you don't expect a lot of clapping.
所以可能没多少人鼓掌喝彩的
Miss Delaney, I find when the spiritual rewards are this great,
delaney小姐 我倒觉得 如果我心灵上有着巨大的安慰
who needs applause?
谁还需要掌声呢
Excuse me.
我离开下
Did Addison talk to you about me?
Addison有和你说起我的事吗？
Oh!I guess not.
哦 看来没有
He's a married man!
他结过婚了啊
- What's wrong with you?!
- 你究竟怎么想的
No,wait! Wait!
等等
- It's not what you think!
- 不是那么回事
He hasn't touched me for three years
就因为你们这些荡货
Carol, if you would just stop throwing things at me, I'll explain!
- Carol你别再扔东西了 听我解释啊
How--how can you explain?!
你怎么解释? 你在勾引我的丈夫!
You're screwing my husband! No, I'm not screwing him!
你怎么解释? 你在勾引我的丈夫!  我没有啊 他是我父亲啊
He's my father!
我没有啊 他是我父亲啊
I'm so sorry.
对不起
I thought you should know, but he didn't want to tell you.
我觉得应该让你知道 但他不肯说
I want to die.
我想死了
- Oh,no.
- 别这样
I do.
我真的这么想
They have clerks for that.
carol 你不用收拾了 店员会收拾的
How old are you?
你多大了？
38.
38岁
We've been married 39 years.
我们结婚39年了
It's been going on from the start.
看来老早就这样了
Believe me, I didn't want to hurt anyone. I just
相信我 我无意去伤害谁
wanted to find my dad.
我只是想找到我的父亲
I'm glad you did,
我替你高兴
but you be careful,sweetheart.
但是你也别太乐观
He's gonna break your heart.
他会伤透你的心的
Andrew,I made an appointment with a therapist for you, me and Danielle.
andrew,我和一个心理医生约好了  给你 我还有danielle作心理辅导
I don't think so.
我不去
This pain that you're feeling is completely natural,
你现在感到痛苦很正常
but it's not gonna go away until you deal with it.
但是你要是不去正视痛苦 就很难摆脱它
Andrew,
Andrew 我希望我们都能 从心灵的创伤中恢复过来
I want us to heal,I want us to be a family again.
Andrew 我希望我们都能 从心灵的创伤中恢复过来  我希望大家还能象一家人一样
You know what I want?
你知道我怎么想吗？
I want for George Williams to walk through that door
我想George Williams能走进来
so I can take a knife and plunge it into his heart.
我好拿把刀 狠狠地刺向他的心脏
I want the pharmacist to pay for what he did to my father.
我要那个家伙血债血偿
Well,the good news is he's...he's dead.
还好他 他已经死了
He committed suicide.
他是自杀 那只能算他自己的
That's not justice.
不能算恶人有恶报
So are you saying if he were
你的意思是如果他是他杀的
executed that it would be easier for you to get past this?
你会好受一点？
Of course.
当然
George...
didn't intend to commit suicide.
本没有打算自杀
He was trying to manipulate meinto taking him back,
他想利用自杀让我回心转意
and he swallowed those pills hoping that I'd feel sorry for him.
他就吞了安眠药 想让我觉得内疚
He just assumed that I would call an ambulance.
他以为我肯定会叫救护车
When I got there,he was already slipping away.
我到房间时 他已经迷糊了
accept responsibility for what he'd done...
我想让他自愿承担自己 所作所为的责任
but he wouldn't.
但他不愿意
So what'd you do?
那么你干吗了？
Nothing.
什么也没做
I just sat there and let him die.
我就坐在那 看着他死去
Oh,my god.
天啊
He didn't die on his terms,andrew.
他不是自杀 andrew
He paid for what he did to your father.
他算为你父亲之死偿命了
Thank you for telling me this.
谢谢你告诉我
Hey, how you doin'?
你好啊
Yeah?
什么事？
Zach's come home.
Zach回来了
What?
什么？他还好吗？
- Is he okay? - He's fine.
什么？他还好吗？  他很好
Is there anything I can do?
我能做些什么？
Thanks for asking.
谢谢你关心
You can leave us alone.
麻烦你不要再来烦我们
I spent a lot of time looking for zach,
我一直在找Zach 你知道原因
- and you know why. - Maybe I'm notmaking myself clear.
我一直在找Zach 你知道原因  我再说明白点吧
You come near my son, I'll go to the police.
你要是胆敢靠近我而已一步 我就报警
I'll tell them what happened out in that quarry.
告诉他们那天在采石场的事
You do that and we'll both go down.
你这么做 我们都完蛋
you know I'm capable of almost anything.
你知道我可以不择手段的
Hey,I thought you'd like to know
对了 另外 Zack和我要搬走
zach and I are moving away.
I want to give my son a shot at a normal life.
我想让我的儿子过正常人的生活
I'm sure you'll agree it's for the best.
我想你也认同我的做法吧
Now see, this is where you and I don't see eye-to-eye.
偏偏就是这点 我不这么看
For zach's sake, I'll keep quiet, for now,
为了Zack 我会保持缄默
but you're not taking him away.
但现在你不可以带走Zack
If I see a "for sale" sign in front of that house,
如果我看见你屋前立了“待售”的牌子
I'll call the police.
我会立刻报警
I'm capable of pretty much anything myself.
我也会不择手段的
the doctor's going to give you a full work-up,
医生会给你作个全面检查
then we'll start the inoculations.
然后进行疫苗注射
Make sure you fill out everything
确保一项不落的填好
- and the nurse will take you back.
- 护士会带你进去的
Thank you.
谢谢
Boy,Sister Mary's done a number on you.
mary修女看来还真好好地“磨炼”你了
- Right. - Yes,right.
是啊  什么是啊？！
She has you flying halfway across the world to help the poor
她竟然让你飞过大半个地球去救济穷人
and there'sperfectly good poor right here.
可我们这里明明就有穷人却不救济！
For god's sakes, give a buck to a homeless guy.
给个一块钱给流浪汉啊
- It's not the same. - No,it's better
不一样的嘛  当然不一样 在这你可以舒服地坐在车上施舍
because you can do it in the comfort of your own car.
当然不一样 在这你可以舒服地坐在车上施舍
The point is not to be comfortable,gaby.
这不是舒服的问题 Gaby
It's about easing pain and suffering.
而是摆脱痛苦和折磨的问题
Look,I'm trying to bea better person here.
我在极力做一个好人
Now you can either help meor you can get out of the way,
你要么帮忙 要不就别碍事
but you can't stop me.
但你是拦不住我的
Carlos Solis?
Come with me,please.
跟我来
Finish that for me.
帮我填完
here.
填好了
He didn't fill out the allergy section.
过敏史一栏没填
Honey,he's going to a remote village in africa.
他是去非洲什么偏远小镇
Does it really matter that he's allergic to eggs?
他对蛋类食物过敏会碍事吗？
Actually,yes.Eggs are on the list.
会的 蛋类食物就在其列
He could have a severe reaction to the yellow fever vaccine,
对黄热病疫苗 他会有严重过敏反应
and he won't be getting out of bed,let alone leaving the country.
连床都下不了 更别说什么出国了
Really?
真的吗？
Oh,don't write that down.
哦 别着急写
I wasn't being specific.
我刚才没详细说
He's allergic to fish eggs.
他对鱼子过敏
Fish eggs?
鱼子？
Poor baby's gone his whole life without caviar.
可怜他一辈子不能吃鱼子酱呢
Now that's suffering.
真是煎熬啊
All right, doc,give me all you got.
好了 医生 注射吧
It's so hot in this village.
镇上好热啊
Baby,that's the fever talking.
亲爱的 你又在说胡话了
The doctor said you're having an allergic reaction,
医生说你过敏了
but you're gonna be fine,okay?
不过你很快就会好起来的
Hold me.
抱着我
Ohh,honey. I'm so sorry.
亲爱的 对不起
Ohh,maybe that stupid nun is right.
也许那个白痴修女是对的
Maybe I am trying to stop you from becoming a better person.
我是在阻碍你成为一个更好的人
It's just that I love you the way you are--
但是我就是喜欢你的
greedy, selfish and insensitive.
贪婪 自私和冷漠
I'm just scared if you're not those things anymore,
我担心这些特质会随之消失
you're gonna wake up one day
担心你有一天突然醒来
and realize I still am,
发现我还是以前那样
and then you won't want me.
就会抛弃我
I want you. Just hold me.
我要你抱着我
Ohh,Carlos.
哦 Carlos
Hold me...
抱着我...
Sister Mary.
Mary修女
Painting in the rain?
下雨了还在刷漆？可不是好主意
Is that smart?
Well,let me see,painting in the rain
不在雨天刷漆难道要让 整个世界的人都认为我是个婊子？
or letting the whole world think I'm a whore?
I don't know.What do you think?
你怎么看啊？
Heard you ran into my wife.
听说你碰到我妻子了
Yep.
是的
So?
那么？
So you are hereby released of any further obligation to be my dad.
那么你从此无须承担为父之责了
Okay.
好吧
Just so you know,
不过对于我过去那些事 那些喜好
I'm not actually proud of what I've done
you know, my hobbies.
我一点也不感到自豪
Good for you.
太好了 再见
Bye.
I have done things I'm proud of.
不过我做过自豪的事
I could give you five examples right now.
我可以给你举五个例子
Okay,maybe three.
好吧 三个
You don't have to do this.
你不用这么做
I was a volunteer fireman.
我自愿当消防队员
I put out fires,I got kittens out of trees,the whole nine yards.
我灭过火  从树上救下过小猫
Sweet.
真好
About 20 years ago,I started a foundation to
20年前 我建立了一个拯救野马的基金会
protect wild horses. I probably saved hundreds of them.
应该挽救了不少马匹了
Really?
真的？
I'm full of surprises.
我这人还是能干点出其不意的事的
Okay,one more.
好吧 还有最后一件事
I wasn't exactly thrilled when you walked back into my life.
当你闯入我的生活时  我一开始并不觉得高兴
Now that I've met you,
但自从见到你
well,you gave me a third thing to be proud of.
你给了我最为自豪的第三件事
That was a good one.
说的好
That's why I saved it for last.
所以我才留到最后说
I have to spend some time working on my marriage.
我得先解决一下我的婚姻问题
maybe we could continue with the
等那忙完了 也许我们能继续叙叙旧？
I'll wait for your call.
我等你电话
The stories are as old as time itself...
故事依旧是那个古老的故事
the prodigal son who returns home
浪子回头金不换
to the father who forgives him...
善父宽容抛前嫌
the jealous wife who tricks the husband who trust her...
欲妻讹夫骗信任
who risks everything for the child who needs her
慈母护子为哪般
who hurts the wife who loves him so deeply.
为夫不忠留妻绝
Why do we listen again and again?
为何故事一遍又一遍
Because these are the stories of family,
只因事关一家人
and once we look past the fighting, pain and the resentment,
蓦然回首
we occasionally like to remind ourselves...
须自省
There is absolutely nothing more important.
家为首